place out there I don't want state prisoners okay they are a necessary evil to keep the doors open
that we keep a few or keep some out there and that's the ones that you can work that's the
ones that can pick up trash the work release programs but guess what those are the ones that
they're releasing in addition to the in addition to the bad ones and I call these bad in addition
to them they're releasing some good ones that we use every day to to wash cars to change oil in our
cars to cook in the kitchen to do all that where we save money well they're gonna let them out so is
it slavery because it's given slavery if it walked like slavery and it talked like slavery and it
sounded like slavery by the way he's talking slavery was on the ballot in Louisiana when we say slavery
was on the ballot the 13th amendment says everybody is free from slavery unless you did some shit that
got you in jail then we can do whatever we want with you it does and so there was during the midterms a
number of states that had this particular clause as it relates to that individual state on their ballot
on their ballot and you know that all of those did not pass yes there are states like Louisiana that was
like no we're gonna keep that in there we're gonna keep that slavery thing let's keep the slavery train
running and it looks like he is on that train going choo choo all aboard